M MANSOUR MAHBOBI

IT engineer Fullstack Python developer

Tehran, Rasht
+98 903 864 55 62
mm.mahboubi@ut.ac.ir
in mansourmahbobi



WHO AM I?

I started my career when I began to learn Gnu/linux. then Opensource technologies becomes my first interest. after learning python during my BSC I tested my development knowledge under production with virakad.com.Lately and after graduation I'm working on Ecmascript and specificly react and mahanhyper.market is the result. I have more than two years experience with web technologies and I'm looking for new opportunities. also I have some freelance experience using react-native and Docker



LPIC-1 LPIC-2 git python react

EXPERIENCE

2019 **fullstack python developer** mahanhyper.market

fullstack python developer and devops. find more at https://mahanhyper.market/

linux / django / react / mysql / celery / nginx

1/2019 - 6/2019 Teacher Assistant - Introduction to database fowman faculty of engineering

assistant for database course in fall 2019

database /

1/2018 - 9/2018 fullstack python developer virakad.com

Cofounder, virakad.com was supposed to be a grocery marketplace.

I was fullstack python developer and responsible for IT infra.

find more at https://virakad.com/

linux / django / bootstrap / mysql / Cpanel

2017 - 1/2018 wordpress developer farsireviews.com

Cofounder, farsireview was a persian magazine and review producer .

I was responsible for It Infrastructure.

find more at https://farsireviews.com/about.
wordpress / php / bootstrap / Cpanel

2015 – 2017 member of IT association Fowman faculty of engineering

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

2019 **python developer** ghalbsefid charity

ghalbsefid profile photo maker for supporters

find more at https://t.me/ghalbsebot
python / Pillow / Docker / sqlite

EDUCATION

2014 – 2019 Bachelor's Degree University of Tehran

Information Technology engineering

Thesis: Intro to devops, and compairing container based virtualization and serverless

EX member of IT association

BSC PROJECTS

12/2015 Advanced Programing University of Tehran

system for managing students in CPP

12/2016 Artificial intelligence University of Tehran

a rival for tic-tac-toe in JAVA

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

3/2019 LPIC-2 ARJANG institute

certificate ID e5khkv6brsyr74vwpw3j

1/2018 LPIC-1 ARJANG institute

certificate ID 992xzjyjss6ih59y4nvt

12/2017 Python Programming ARJANG institute

certificate ID se5gmateouym2rorblxw

12/2017 Introduction to writing business plan University of Tehran

a course which i was a member of operation team

10/2015 Introduction to web programming University of Tehran

a course which i was a member of operation team

10/2015 Introduction to trading Tehran Institute Of Technology

amateur trading using technical analysis

LANGUAGES HOBBIES

Persian - native I love running, biking and building simpler life using new technologies

English - proficient and also I trade in TSE as a hobby.